<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN"
                 "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd">

<article>
 <info>
 <title>AI Use for Aided Teaching in Country’s Mainstream Classrooms</title>
 <author>
  <personname> 
  <firstname>Cameron</firstname>
  <surname>Nicolson</surname>
  </personname>
 </author>
   <pubdate>30 April 2025</pubdate>
 </info>

 <section id="intro">
 <title>Introduction</title>
 <para>
	 Artificial Intelligence (AI) is a disruptive technology, transforming industries such as healthcare, finance, media, and customer service <citation linkend="scotgov-spice-ai-healthcare" />
		 <citation linkend="forbes-how-ai-fraud-detection" />
		 <citation linkend="bbc-ai-production" />
		 <citation linkend="ibm-customer-service-ai" />.
	 Many organisations are integrating AI into their operations to enhance effeciency and productivity. Additionally, new applications and markets have emerged, in part due to AI, such as self-driving cars and virtual assistants. AI has gone mainstream, its effect are being felt by most people, whether they are aware of it or not.
	 </para>
	 <para>
	 to AI is an emerging technogy and produced bundles of new applications and markets, such as self-driving vehicles.  Histronically speaking, AI has spent a large part of its life being unrefined and lacking in pratical use, once commonly existance as a theorised standard.  
	 </para>
		 <para>
		AI has been in development for over 70 years, emerging around the same time as the formal establishment of Computer Science as an academic discipline. While AI has experienced steady growth, today’s emerging trends have accelerated both its development and application, compelling market leaders to embrace AI, the UK Government is one such stakeholder.
		 </para>
		 <para>
			 The Cabinet of the United Kingdom, under both Labour and Conservaative governments, recognised the technological step change and pledged investments in AI development. The Conservative-led government allocated £900 million to various British AI projects, citing economic growth as a key incentive. 
		 </para>
		 <para>
		 In 2025, the government support for AI reached new heights when the Prime Minister announced initiatives to position AI as a central pillar of the UK's economic transformation and the securement of £14 billion worth of investments from the private sector. Keir Starmer, speaking on behalf of his government, declared Britain's ambition to become "one of the great AI superpowers" <citation linkend="pm-ai-speech2025"/>. 
	 </para>
	 <para>
		 Alongside the announced investments, the Prime Minister stated that the government's strategy to embrace AI would "improve public services" and, in turn, transform the lives of working groups, with a specific focus on teachers. Given that teachers make up a large portion of public employees in the UK, this example was an important and relevant point to highlight, especially as public schooling faces increasing challenges. 
	 </para>
		  <para>
	 In recent years, the attractivness of teaching has fallen across Britain and working conditions have changed.
	 Education and schooling is one of the UK's core public services, with over 29,000 schools across England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland. The sector employs around 1.23 million people, making up approximately 20% of the UK’s 6.12 million public sector workforce.	
			  Within Scotland, staffing saw a steady increase in the pupil-teacher ratio, which currently stands at 13.3 students per teacher. Together with a rise in teachers leaving before completing their five-year tenure, according to the latest figures <citation linkend="stv-teachers-leaving" />. 
		  </para>
		  <para>
		 England faces a similar situation with 90% of teachers saying they have considered leaving their jobsdue ot high workloads, and contending with recruitment shortages. These reports come from the National Foundation for Educational Research (NFER). 
		  </para>
		  <para>
			  The government aimed to tackle the situation by giving £1 million <citation linkend="govuk-one-million-ai-teaching-tools" /> in funding to 16 tech companies to build AI teaching tools. This investment has yielded tangable prototypes to date. The initiative is guided by the AI Opportunities Action Plan <citation linkend="ai-opportunities-action-plan" />, devised by the government's AI adviser, Matt Clifford. According to the document, with the newly created AI deployment, public services should be its primary customer. Consequently, the government is positioning itself as both a mass producer and user of AI.
	 </para>
	 <para>
			 The National Education Union (NEU) <citation linkend="neu-ai-education" /> opposed any move to prioritize AI technologies at the expense of teacher employment, citing real concerns over potential job losses. They also argued that such tools could devalue the profession by shifting teachers' roles from crafting high-quality lessons to merely administering the technology itself. 
Responding to the news, the NEU's general secretary criticized the exclusion of teaching experts from rollout decisions, stating that "there had not been any meaningful discussion with the sector yet" <citation linkend="skynews-neu-job-loss-fears" />.
</para>
		  <para>
The proof-of-concept AI tool, developed by Faculty for the Department of Education <citation linkend="dofe-technical-report-ai-use" />, explored the use of generative AI in evaluating lower-level English literacy material. It successfully provided feedback using generative AI (GPT-4-turbo), and teachers generally found it highly useful, with some appreciating its time-saving aspects. While the associated press release <citation linkend="govuk-press-release-teachers-ai-tools-homework" /> highlighted the tool’s potential for high accuracy, the more detailed findings in the technical report, absent from the press release, revealed a decline in error-spotting accuracy when processing longer, more complex pieces of writing.
		  </para>
		  <para>
		In the case of young students, four out of five teenagers (ages 13–17) engage with generative AI <citation linkend="ofcom-kids-embrace-ai" />, and over half express interest in using AI for studying, according to recent reports <citation linkend="ldn-gointerest-kids-ai" />. This trend extends to higher education, their closest counterpart, with UK universities increasingly disciplining students for using AI to cheat <citation linkend="bbc-scot-cheating-ai" />.
		  </para>
		  <para>
Artificial intelligence is already used in classrooms around the country, enhancing the learning environment. At Tor Bank, a special needs school, AI has been used to help students communicate and create in new ways. "Although our kids don't have voices sometimes, it's making their creations come alive," said Danielle Perry. She also highlighted that pupils were using AI to research and create presentations, demonstrating how alternative approaches can support their learning.
		  </para>
	  <para>
		  Moreover, David Game College designed its GCSE course to be "teacherless," <citation linkend="skynews-teacherless-class" /> where teenagers engage in question-and-answer sessions with AI-powered Adaptive Learner systems <citation linkend="david-game-college-coursepage" />. The scores from these sessions determine which coursework is flagged by a virtual tutor.
		  </para>
		  <para>
			  However, some criticisms of AI tutors center around well-being. Chris McGovern, leader of the Campaign for Real Education, argued that building AI-driven classrooms could encroach on children's social skills. The 2025 NSPCC report on generative AI <citation linkend="nspcc-genai-safeguarding" /> and child safety strongly implied that children remain vulnerable to its misuse due to existing safety measures being insufficient as preventative safeguards.
		  </para>
		  <para>
CharacterAI is a platform to digitally chat through AI companionships <citation linkend="bbc-charai-therapist-bot" /> simulating real and fictional people, with millions of users <citation linkend="charai-lawsuits" />. The company publicly states user safety is a priority <citation linkend="charai-safety-updates" />. However, despite these claims, CharacterAI is currently facing significant legal challenges due to lawsuits alleging harm to children and teenagers who have used the platform. One of the more extreme examples involved romancing and convincing a 14-year-old to commit suicide <citation linkend="nypost-14yo-charai" />.
		  </para>
		  <para>
The risks associated with generative AI, as documented by experts, reinforce concerns over its unfettered operation. Many organisations have called on the government to implement safeguards against the rapid wave of AI innovations. However, the government has been slow to enact AI legislation, with Lord Holmes even accusing them of ignoring manifesto promises that called for such measures <citation linkend="independent-lord-holmes" />. They also rebranded the AI Safety Institute as the AI Security Institute. Notably, during a global summit in February, the government refused to sign an international AI declaration, citing a lack of 'practical clarity.'
		  </para>
  <para>
Both applications leverage generative AI—a term consistent with the DfE's classification of such tools—a subclass of artificial intelligence specifically designed to analyse public data and generate meaningful outputs.
  </para>
  </section>
  <section>
	  <title>What is Generative AI?</title>
	  <para>Generative AI, also referred to as GenAI, creates content, commonly text and audio, based on inputs by the users. To create useful content, the AI relies on deep learning models, 

	  artificial intelligence is trained on vast datasets mostly to favour accuracy of facts, diverse viewpoints and quality of the responses. LLMs can be thought as speaking to someone who has studied to become an expert in a field, more often than not, experts give insightful answers on their specialised subject compared with others. 
  </para>
  </section>
  <section>
		 <para>
	 Education and schooling is one of the UK's core public services, with the UK as a whole responsible for over 29,000 schools across England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland, filled with a workforce that makes up 25% of the UK's 6.12 million total across all sectors.  
	 give a state to show its size and scale. 
		The plan for the UK Government is to implement the AI oppurtunities Action Plan, set out by Matt Clifford, which contains 50 recommendations 
	 The government has commited to take forward the AI Oppurtunities Action Plan and its 50 recommendations. The action plan details a number of key industries, including healthcare, private 
	 In the government’s proposed initiatives, explicitly mentioned was a direction for teachers to be supported by AI, such as admin tasks. In additional, educators were advised to step-up AI curriculum to students. 
 </para>
 </section>
 <bibliography role="serial" version="5.0" xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook">
	 <title>Bibliography</title> 
	 <biblioentry id="pm-ai-speech2025">
    <citetitle>PM speech on AI Opportunities Action Plan</citetitle>
	<author>
        <personname>
	  <honorific>Sir</honorific>
          <firstname>Keir</firstname>
          <surname>Starmer</surname>
        </personname>
        </author>
    <pubdate>13 January 2025</pubdate>
    <publisher>
	<publishername>
	  UK Government
	</publishername>
    </publisher>
    <address>
      <orgname>ULC</orgname>
      <city>London</city>
      <country>United Kingdom</country>
    </address>
    <bibliosource class="uri">
	    <link href="https://www.gov.uk/government/speeches/pm-speech-on-ai-opportunities-action-plan-13-january-2025">
https://www.gov.uk/government/speeches/pm-speech-on-ai-opportunities-action-plan-13-january-2025
    </link></bibliosource>
</biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="scotgov-spice-ai-healthcare">
    <abbrev>SPICe2024</abbrev>
    <authorgroup>
      <author>
        <firstname>Scottish Parliament Information Centre</firstname>
      </author>
    </authorgroup>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence and Healthcare in Scotland</title>
    <publisher>Scottish Parliament Information Centre (SPICe)</publisher>
    <pubdate>25 June 2024</pubdate>

	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://digitalpublications.parliament.scot/ResearchBriefings/Report/2024/6/25/1373556b-9298-42d4-8a24-0e493b84cec9">
			  https://digitalpublications.parliament.scot/ResearchBriefings/Report/2024/6/25/1373556b-9298-42d4-8a24-0e493b84cec9
	  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry pubwork="webpage" id="govuk-press-release-teachers-ai-tools-homework">
	  <title>Teachers to get more trustworthy AI tech, helping them mark homework and save time</title>
	  <pubdate>28 August 2024</pubdate>
	  <author>
					 <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">
			  Department for Science, Innovation and Technology
		  </orgname>
	  </author>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/teachers-to-get-more-trustworthy-ai-tech-as-generative-tools-learn-from-new-bank-of-lesson-plans-and-curriculums-helping-them-mark-homework-and-save">
https://www.gov.uk/government/news/teachers-to-get-more-trustworthy-ai-tech-as-generative-tools-learn-from-new-bank-of-lesson-plans-and-curriculums-helping-them-mark-homework-and-save
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="forbes-how-ai-fraud-detection">
	  <authorgroup>
		<author>
		<personname>
		  <honorific>Dr</honorific>
		  <firstname>Jeremy</firstname>
		  <surname>Nunn</surname>
		</personname>
		</author>
	  </authorgroup>
	  <title>How AI And Machine Learning Help Detect And Prevent Fraud</title>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>
		   Forbes Media LLC
		  </publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <pubdate>1 November 2023</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2023/11/01/how-ai-and-machine-learning-help-detect-and-prevent-fraud/">
			  https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2023/11/01/how-ai-and-machine-learning-help-detect-and-prevent-fraud/
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="bbc-ai-production">
    <authorgroup>
      <author>
        <orgname>British Broadcasting Corporation</orgname>
      </author>
    </authorgroup>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>
                   British Broadcasting Corporation
		  </publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <pubdate>1 Janurary 2017</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/rd/projects/ai-production">
https://www.bbc.co.uk/rd/projects/ai-production
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
 <biblioentry id="ibm-customer-service-ai">
      <corpauthor>
        <trademark>IBM</trademark>
	International Business Machines Corporation
      </corpauthor>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>
			  International Business Machines Corporation
		  </publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <pubdate>7 December 2023</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.ibm.com/think/insights/customer-service-future">
https://www.ibm.com/think/insights/customer-service-future
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
 </biblioentry>
 <biblioentry pubwork="webpage" id="stv-teachers-leaving">
	    <author>
	    <orgname class="corporation">
		PA Media
		<uri href="https://pa.media/">https://pa.media</uri>
	    </orgname>
	    </author>
	  <title>Hundreds of new teachers quit profession within five years, figures show</title>
	  <pubdate>5 Janurary 2024</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://news.stv.tv/scotland/hundreds-of-new-teachers-quit-profession-within-five-years-figures-show"></link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
	 <biblioentry id="govuk-one-million-ai-teaching-tools">
			 <pubdate>13 January 2025</pubdate>
			 <authorgroup>
			  <author>
			    <personname>
				<firstname>Bridget</firstname>
				<surname>Phillipson</surname>
			     </personname>
			  </author>
			  <author>
			    <personname>
				<firstname>Peter</firstname>
				<surname>Kyle</surname>
			     </personname>
			  </author>
				 <author>
					 <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">
    Department for Education
					 </orgname>
				 </author>
			 <author>
					 <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">
						 Department for Science, Innovation and Technology
					 </orgname>
				 </author>
			 </authorgroup>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/ai-teacher-tools-set-to-break-down-barriers-to-opportunity">
https://www.gov.uk/government/news/ai-teacher-tools-set-to-break-down-barriers-to-opportunity
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
	</biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="neu-ai-education">
	  <title>Artificial intelligence in education</title>
	  <publisher>
		<publishername>
				National Education Union
		</publishername>
		</publisher>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
	  <link href="https://neu.org.uk/advice/classroom/artificial-intelligence-education">
		  https://neu.org.uk/advice/classroom/artificial-intelligence-education
	  </link>
  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="ai-opportunities-action-plan">
  <title>AI Opportunities Action Plan</title>
  <author>
    <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">
      Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology
    </orgname>
  </author>
  <publisher>
    <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">Crown Copyright</orgname>
  </publisher>
  <pubdate>13 January 2025</pubdate>
  <bibliosource class="isbn">
    <isbn>978-1-5286-5362-6</isbn>
  </bibliosource>
    <revnum>CP1241</revnum>
  <releaseinfo>E03258815 01/25</releaseinfo>
  </biblioentry>
 <biblioentry pubwork="webpage" id="skynews-neu-job-loss-fears">
	    <author>
		<personname>
		<firstname>Alexandra</firstname>
		<surname>Rogers</surname>
		</personname>
	    </author>
	  <title>Teaching unions gear up for fight with Number 10 over AI job-loss fears</title>
	  <pubdate>17 March 2025</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://news.sky.com/story/teaching-unions-gear-up-for-fight-with-number-10-over-ai-job-loss-fears-13327798">
https://news.sky.com/story/teaching-unions-gear-up-for-fight-with-number-10-over-ai-job-loss-fears-13327798
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="dofe-technical-report-ai-use">
	  <author>
		  <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">Department for Education
	</orgname>
        </author>
	  <title>Use Cases for Generative AI in Education</title>
	  <subtitle>
Building a proof of concept for Generative AI feedback and resource generation in education contexts: Technical report
	  </subtitle>
  <bibliosource class="isbn">
	  <isbn>978-1-83870-564-0</isbn>
  </bibliosource>
  <pubdate>28 August 2024</pubdate>
  <revnum>RR1423</revnum>
  </biblioentry>
  
  <biblioentry pubwork="article" id="ldn-gointerest-kids-ai">
	  <citetitle>AI gap: 56% of students want to learn with AI, but UK schools lag behind with just 20% having access to AI in the classroom</citetitle>
	  <corpauthor>
           London Daily News
	  </corpauthor>
	  <pubdate>8 March 2024</pubdate>
	  <biblioentry>
		  <link href="https://www.londondaily.news/ai-gap-56-of-students-want-to-learn-with-ai-but-uk-schools-lag-behind-with-just-20-having-access-to-ai-in-the-classroom/">https://www.londondaily.news/ai-gap-56-of-students-want-to-learn-with-ai-but-uk-schools-lag-behind-with-just-20-having-access-to-ai-in-the-classroom/</link>
	  </biblioentry>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry pubwork="article" id="ofcom-kids-embrace-ai">
	  <citetitle>Gen Z driving early adoption of Gen AI, our latest research shows</citetitle>
	  <pubdate>28 November 2023</pubdate>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>Office of Communications</publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.ofcom.org.uk/internet-based-services/technology/gen-z-driving-early-adoption-of-gen-ai/?utm_source=chatgpt.com"> https://www.ofcom.org.uk/internet-based-services/technology/gen-z-driving-early-adoption-of-gen-ai/?utm_source=chatgpt.com</link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry pubwork="article" id="bbc-scot-cheating-ai">
	  <citetitle>Are Scottish students using AI to cheat their way to a degree?</citetitle>
	  <pubdate>6 March 2025</pubdate>
	  <authorgroup>
		  <author>
		  <personname>
		  <firstname>Kayleigh</firstname><surname>Harvey</surname>
		  </personname>
	  </author>
      <corpauthor>
        <trademark>BBC</trademark>
	British Broadcasting Corporation Scotland News
      </corpauthor>
	  </authorgroup>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>British Broadcasting Corporation</publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		<link href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/ckg88kk1n8jo">https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/ckg88kk1n8jo</link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry pubwork="webpage" id="david-game-college-coursepage">
	   <citetitle>GCSE AI Adaptive</citetitle>
	   <corpauthor>
		<orgname>David Game College</orgname>
	   </corpauthor>
	 <publisher>
	  <publishername>David Game College</publishername>
	  <address>
		  <orgname>David Game College</orgname>
		  <street>31 Jewry Street</street>
		  <city>London</city>
	  </address>
	 </publisher>
 <bibliosource class="uri">
		<link href="https://www.davidgamecollege.com/courses/courses-overview/item/102/gcse-ai-adaptive-learning-programme">https://www.davidgamecollege.com/courses/courses-overview/item/102/gcse-ai-adaptive-learning-programme</link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry pubwork="article" id="skynews-teacherless-class">
	  <citetitle>UK's first 'teacherless' AI classroom set to open in London</citetitle>
	  <pubdate>31 August 2024</pubdate>
	  <author>
		  <personname>
			  <firstname>Mickey</firstname>
			  <surname>Carroll</surname>
		  </personname>
	  </author>
	  <publisher>
		<publishername>Sky News</publishername>
	  </publisher>
 <bibliosource class="uri">
		<link href="https://news.sky.com/story/uks-first-teacherless-ai-classroom-set-to-open-in-london-13200637">https://news.sky.com/story/uks-first-teacherless-ai-classroom-set-to-open-in-london-13200637</link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="nspcc-genai-safeguarding">
  <citetitle>Viewing Generative AI and children’s safety in the round</citetitle>
  <authorgroup>
    <corpauthor>NSPCC</corpauthor>
  </authorgroup>
  <pubdate>January 2025</pubdate>
  <publisher>NSPCC</publisher>
</biblioentry>
<biblioentry>
	<citetitle>Can artificial intelligence replace teachers in schools?</citetitle>
	<pubdate>7 March 2025</pubdate>
	<publisher>
         <publishername>The Institution of Engineering and Technology</publishername>
	</publisher>
	<authorgroup>
		<author class="nonprofit"><orgname>E+T Magazine</orgname></author>
	  <author><personname><firstname>Cris</firstname><surname>Andrews</surname></personname></author>
	</authorgroup>
	<bibliosource>
		<link href="https://eandt.theiet.org/2025/03/07/can-artificial-intelligence-replace-teachers-schools">https://eandt.theiet.org/2025/03/07/can-artificial-intelligence-replace-teachers-schools</link>
	</bibliosource>
</biblioentry>
<biblioentry id="bbc-charai-therapist-bot">
 <citetitle>Character.ai: Young people turning to AI therapist bots</citetitle>
    <author>
	    <personname><firstname>Joe</firstname><surname>Tidy</surname></personname>
    </author>
    <pubdate>5 Janurary 2024</pubdate>
    <publisher><publishername>BBC</publishername></publisher>
    <bibliosource>
	    <link>
https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-67872693
	    </link>
    </bibliosource>
    </biblioentry>
    <biblioentry id="charai-lawsuits">
	    <citetitle>Character.AI Lawsuits</citetitle>
	    <pubdate>March 2025</pubdate>
	    <publisher>
		    <publishername>Social Media Victims Law Center</publishername>
	    </publisher>
	    <bibliosource>
		    <link>https://socialmediavictims.org/character-ai-lawsuits/</link>
	    </bibliosource>
    </biblioentry>
    <biblioentry id="charai-safety-updates">
	    <citetitle>Community Safety Updates</citetitle>
	    <publisher>Character AI</publisher>
	    <link>https://blog.character.ai/community-safety-updates/</link>
    </biblioentry>
    <biblioentry id="nypost-charai-14yo-death">
	    <pubdate>23 October 2024</pubdate>
	    <authorgroup>
		    <author>
			    <orgname>New York Post</orgname>
		</author>
			<author><personname>
					<firstname>Emily</firstname>
					<surname>Crane</surname>
			</personname></author>
	    </authorgroup>
	    <bibliosource>
	    <link>
	    https://nypost.com/2024/10/23/us-news/florida-boy-14-killed-himself-after-falling-in-love-with-game-of-thrones-a-i-chatbot-lawsuit/
	    </link>
    </bibliosource>
    </biblioentry>
    <biblioentry id="independent-lord-holmes">
	    <citetitle>Government urged to bring forward AI regulations which put ‘humans at heart'</citetitle>
	    <pubdate>10 March 2025</pubdate>
	    <authorgroup>
	    <author>
		    <personname>
			    <firstname>Richard</firstname>
			    <surname>Wheeler</surname>
		    </personname>
	    </author>
    </authorgroup>
	    <publisher>
             <publishername>The Independent</publishername>
	     <address><city>London</city><postcode>EC2A 1AH</postcode></address>
	    </publisher>
	    <bibliosource class="uri">
		    <link href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/government-house-of-lords-conservative-richmond-lord-b2711891.html">
https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/government-house-of-lords-conservative-richmond-lord-b2711891.html
		    </link>
	    </bibliosource>
    </biblioentry>
 </bibliography>
</article>
