<?xml version='1.0'?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN"
                 "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd">

<article>
 <info>
 <title>AI Use for Aided Teaching in Country’s Mainstream Classrooms</title>
 <author>
  <personname> 
  <firstname>Cameron</firstname>
  <surname>Nicolson</surname>
  </personname>
 </author>
   <pubdate>28 March 2025</pubdate>
 </info>

 <section id="intro">
 <title>Introduction</title>
 <para>
	 Artificial Intelligence (AI) is a disruptive technology, transforming industries such as healthcare, finance, media, and customer service <citation>[<xref linkend="scotgov-spice-ai-healthcare" />,
		 <xref linkend="forbes-how-ai-fraud-detection" />,
		 <xref linkend="bbc-ai-production" />,
		 <xref linkend="ibm-customer-service-ai" />
		 ]</citation>.
	 Many organisations are integrating AI into their operations to enhance efficiency and productivity. Additionally, new applications and markets have emerged, in part due to AI, such as self-driving cars. AI has gone mainstream, its effect are being felt by most people, whether they are aware of it or not.
	 </para>
	<para>
			The development of AI began over 70 years <citation linkend="ai-history" />, throughout its history, it has achieved spectacular feats, including challenging humans in chess and defeating a Grandmaster in 1988 <xref linkend="deep-thought-wins" xlink:href="#deep-thought-wins" />; making phone calls with natural-sounding synthetic voices, such as booking a restaurant table during a live event in 2018 <citation linkend="theverge-google-restaurant" />. Then in 2022, ChatGPT’s ability to engage in human-like conversations, matched with remarkable intelligence, propelled it to phenomenal status, driving major investment and competition in generative AI <citation linkend="wired-google-frenzy"></citation>.
		</para>
		<para>
Generative AI has gained rapid adoption, impressing both users and businesses. The current focus is now on its successful integration, as well as the challenges of introducing AI safely and productively.
As highlighted by McKinsey's global survey <citation linkend="mckinsey-global-ai-survey"><xref linkend="mckinsey-global-ai-survey"></xref></citation>, over three-quarters of organisations report using AI in at least one business function, with the use of generative AI increasing particularly rapidly. Following this widespread initial adoption, the focus for many companies is now increasingly on how to structure their AI initiatives to achieve meaningful financial benefits.
	</para>
</section>
 <section>
  <info>
	  <title>What is Generative AI?</title>
  </info>
  <para>
Generative AI, also referred to as GenAI, instantly generates content on demand, fulfilling entire user requests, such as "Make me a short film with pirates in space." When responding to user prompts, Generative AI analyses patterns in human language using deep learning and probability models to generate the most appropriate response.
  </para>
  <para>
The primary benefit of generative AI is its efficiency. It provides users with instant answers to their questions and can generate entire outputs, such as spreadsheets or programming code. This allows organizations to free up labor from repetitive tasks and focus on more critical work.
  </para>
  </section>
  <section>
	  <title>AI in the public sector</title>
		 <para>
			 The Cabinets of the United Kingdom, under both Labour and Conservative governments, recognised this technological shift and pledged significant investments. The Conservative-led government, allocated £900 million to British AI projects <citation linkend="govuk-invest-ai-taskforce" />, increased spending on related research, and backed the implementation of supercomputers to help with the intensive computational tasks of AI <citation linkend="govuk-supercomputers" />. 
		 </para>
		 <para>
			 After taking office in 2024, the Labour government swiftly moved to cancel Edinburgh University's supercomputer project <citation linkend="bbc-edinburgh-shelved" />. Shortly after, the Prime Minister announced new initiatives to position AI as a central pillar of the UK's economic transformation. The government secured £14 billion in private investments and committed more spending to help realise this vision, signalling a strong shift in policy. Prime Minster Keir Starmer, speaking on behalf of the government, declared that Britain aims to become "one of the great AI superpowers" <xref linkend="pm-ai-speech2025" endterm="pm-ai-speech2025_title" />. 
		 </para>
	 <para>
		 Alongside the announced investments, the Prime Minister stated that the government's strategy to embrace AI would "improve public services" and, in turn, transform the lives of working groups, with a specific focus on teachers. Given that teachers make up a large portion of public employees in the UK, this example was an important and relevant point to highlight, especially as public schooling faces increasing challenges. 
	 </para>
<para>
Education and schooling is one of the UK's core public services, with over 29,000 schools across the entire UK. The sector employs around 1.23 million people, making up approximately 20% of the UK’s 6.12 million public sector workforce.	
In recent years, however, the attractiveness of teaching has fallen across Britain and working conditions have worsened.
		  Within Scotland, staffing saw a steady increase in the pupil-teacher ratio, which currently stands at 13.3 students per teacher. The compensation of teachers is at risk too, with a rise in teachers leaving before completing their five-year tenure, according to the latest figures <citation linkend="stv-teachers-leaving" />. 
		  </para>
<para>
England faces a similar situation with a massive teacher recruitment shortage forecasted, and for the teachers currently employed, job dissatisfaction is severe, with 90% saying they have considered leaving their jobs due to high workloads. These reports came from the National Foundation for Educational Research (NFER). 
</para>
<para>
The government aimed to tackle the situation by providing £1 million <citation linkend='govuk-one-million-ai-teaching-tools' /> in funding to develop AI teaching tools. This investment has so far yielded tangible prototypes. The initiative is guided by the AI Opportunities Action Plan <citation linkend='ai-opportunities-action-plan' />, devised by the government's AI adviser, Matt Clifford. According to the document, the newly created AI deployment is intended to prioritise public services as its primary customer. Additionally, the government has acknowledged that AI could replace certain civil service jobs, estimating significant reductions in the workforce over time <citation linkend="skynews-civil" />.
</para>
<para>
The National Education Union (NEU) <citation linkend="neu-ai-education" /> opposes moves to prioritise AI technologies at the expense of teacher employment, citing real concerns over weakening job security. They also argued that such tools devalue the profession by shifting teachers' roles from crafting high-quality lessons to merely administering the technology itself. 
Responding to the Prime Minister's speech, the NEU's general secretary criticised the exclusion of teaching experts from roll-out decisions, stating that "there had not been any meaningful discussion with the sector yet" <citation linkend="skynews-neu-job-loss-fears" />.
</para>
</section>
<section>
	<title>Current AI tools in practise</title>
		  <para>
The proof-of-concept AI tool, developed by Faculty for the Department of Education <citation linkend="dofe-technical-report-ai-use" />, explored the use of generative AI in evaluating lower-level English literacy material. It successfully provided feedback using GPT-4-turbo, and teachers generally found it highly useful, with some appreciating its time-saving aspects. While the associated press release <citation linkend="govuk-press-release-teachers-ai-tools-homework" /> highlighted the tool’s potential for high accuracy, the more detailed findings in the technical report, absent from the press release, revealed a decline in error-spotting accuracy when processing longer, more complex pieces of writing.
		  </para>
		  <para>
		In the case of young students, four out of five teenagers (ages 13–17) engage with generative AI <citation linkend="ofcom-kids-embrace-ai" />, and over half express interest in using AI for studying, according to recent reports <citation linkend="ldn-gointerest-kids-ai" />. This trend extends to higher education, their closest counterpart, with UK universities increasingly disciplining students for using AI to cheat <citation linkend="bbc-scot-cheating-ai" />.
		  </para>
		  <para>
Artificial intelligence is already used in classrooms around the country, enhancing children's learning. At Tor Bank, a special needs school, AI has been used to help students communicate and be more creative. "Although our kids don't have voices sometimes, it's making their creations come alive," said Danielle Perry. She also highlighted that pupils were using AI to research and create presentations, demonstrating how alternative approaches can support their learning.
		  </para>
	  <para>
		  Moreover, David Game College designed a GCSE course to be "teacherless," <citation linkend="skynews-teacherless-class" /> where teenagers engage in one-on-one sessions with tech. Their AI-powered Adaptive Learner systems <citation linkend="david-game-college-coursepage" /> scores from these sessions to determine which coursework is flagged by a virtual tutor.
		  </para>
		  <para>
			  However, critics of AI tutors mostly center around the children's well-being. Chris McGovern, leader of the Campaign for Real Education, argued that building AI-driven classrooms could encroach on children's social skills. The 2025 NSPCC report on generative AI <citation linkend="nspcc-genai-safeguarding" /> and child safety, strongly implied that children remain vulnerable to the technology's misuse due to companies existing insufficient safety measures.
		  </para>
		  <para>
Character AI is a platform to digitally chat through AI companionships <citation linkend="bbc-charai-therapist-bot" /> simulating real and fictional people, with millions of users <citation linkend="charai-lawsuits" />. The company publicly states user safety is a priority <citation linkend="charai-safety-updates" />. However, despite these claims, CharacterAI is currently facing significant legal challenges due to lawsuits alleging harm to children and teenagers who have used the platform. One of the more extreme examples involved romancing and convincing a 14-year-old to commit suicide <citation linkend="nypost-14yo-charai" />.
		  </para>
		  <para>
The risks associated with generative AI, as documented by experts, reinforce concerns over its unfettered operation. Many organisations have called on the government to implement safeguards against the rapid wave of AI innovations. However, the government has been slow to enact AI legislation, with Lord Holmes even accusing them of ignoring manifesto promises that called for such measures <citation linkend="independent-lord-holmes" />. They also rebranded the AI Safety Institute as the AI Security Institute. Notably, during a global summit in February, the government refused to sign an international AI declaration, citing a lack of "practical clarity."
		  </para>
  </section>
  <section>
	  <title>Conclusion</title>
	  <para> 
The government's long-term support for AI has set the public sector on a path toward greater adoption. These initiatives were introduced to drive economic growth. However, this support has prompted unionised groups to defend job opportunities for teachers.
	  </para>
<para>
	Furthermore, generative AI is now firmly in the public consciousness, with both teachers and students increasingly inclined to use the technology. Its benefits include enhancing learning environments by providing students with more ways to engage with the curriculum and allowing teachers to focus on higher-value tasks
</para>
	  <para>
		  Although AI has shown positive outcomes, critics argued that its impact on productivity could be a false economy. Regarding safety, concerns were raised about the risks for children proactively engaging with AI, particularly the potential for coercion of vulnerable children. Some experts advocated for a more proactive government response, believing that new legislation was necessary to protect people from the realities of AI.
	  </para>
  </section>
   <bibliography role="serial">
  <title>Bibliography</title> 
  <biblioentry xreflabel="1" id="scotgov-spice-ai-healthcare">
    <citetitle>Artificial Intelligence and Healthcare in Scotland</citetitle>
    <authorgroup>
      <author>
        <orgname>Scottish Parliament Information Centre</orgname>
      </author>
    </authorgroup>
    <publisher>Scottish Parliament Information Centre (SPICe)</publisher>
    <pubdate>25 June 2024</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://digitalpublications.parliament.scot/ResearchBriefings/Report/2024/6/25/1373556b-9298-42d4-8a24-0e493b84cec9">
			  https://digitalpublications.parliament.scot/ResearchBriefings/Report/2024/6/25/1373556b-9298-42d4-8a24-0e493b84cec9
	  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>

  <biblioentry xreflabel="2" id="forbes-how-ai-fraud-detection">
	  <authorgroup>
		<author>
		<personname>
		  <honorific>Dr</honorific>
		  <firstname>Jeremy</firstname>
		  <surname>Nunn</surname>
		</personname>
		</author>
	  </authorgroup>
	  <title>How AI And Machine Learning Help Detect And Prevent Fraud</title>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>
		   Forbes Media LLC
		  </publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <pubdate>1 November 2023</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2023/11/01/how-ai-and-machine-learning-help-detect-and-prevent-fraud/">
			  https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2023/11/01/how-ai-and-machine-learning-help-detect-and-prevent-fraud/
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>

  <biblioentry xreflabel="3" id="bbc-ai-production">
    <authorgroup>
      <author>
        <orgname>British Broadcasting Corporation</orgname>
      </author>
    </authorgroup>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>
                   British Broadcasting Corporation
		  </publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <pubdate>1 Janurary 2017</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/rd/projects/ai-production">
https://www.bbc.co.uk/rd/projects/ai-production
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>

 <biblioentry xreflabel="4" id="ibm-customer-service-ai">
      <corpauthor>
        <trademark>IBM</trademark>
	International Business Machines Corporation
      </corpauthor>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>
			  International Business Machines Corporation
		  </publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <pubdate>7 December 2023</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.ibm.com/think/insights/customer-service-future">
https://www.ibm.com/think/insights/customer-service-future
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
 </biblioentry>

 <biblioentry xml:id="wired-google-frenzy">
  <citetitle>Inside Google’s Two-Year Frenzy to Catch Up With OpenAI</citetitle>
  <pubdate>22 March 2025</pubdate>
  <authorgroup>
    <author>
      <firstname>Paresh</firstname>
      <surname>Dave</surname>
    </author>
    <author>
      <firstname>Arielle</firstname>
      <surname>Pardes</surname>
    </author>
  </authorgroup>
  <publisher>
    <publishername>WIRED</publishername>
  </publisher>
  <bibliosource class="uri">
	  <link href="https://www.wired.com/story/google-openai-gemini-chatgpt-artificial-intelligence/">
		  https://www.wired.com/story/google-openai-gemini-chatgpt-artificial-intelligence/?utm_source=chatgpt.com
	  </link>
  </bibliosource>
</biblioentry>

<biblioentry xreflabel="6" xml:id="mckinsey-global-ai-survey">
  <citetitle>The state of AI: How organizations are rewiring to capture value</citetitle>
  <author>
    <orgname>McKinsey and Company</orgname>
  </author>
  <publisher>
	  <publishername>McKinsey and Company</publishername>
  </publisher>
  <pubdate>12 March 2025</pubdate>
  <bibliosource>
	  <link xlink:href="https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/quantumblack/our-insights/the-state-of-ai">
https://www.mckinsey.com/capabilities/quantumblack/our-insights/the-state-of-ai
	  </link>
  </bibliosource>
</biblioentry>

<biblioentry xml:id="ibm-what-is-gen-ai">
	<citetitle>What is generative AI?</citetitle>
	<pubdate>22 March 2024</pubdate>
	<authorgroup>
	<author>
		<personname>
			<firstname>Mark</firstname>
			<surname>Scapicchio</surname>
		</personname>
	</author>
	<author>
		<personname>
			<firstname>Cole</firstname>
			<surname>Stryker</surname>
		</personname>
	</author>
	</authorgroup>
	<bibliosource>
	<link xlink:href="https://www.ibm.com/think/topics/generative-ai">
		https://www.ibm.com/think/topics/generative-ai
	</link>
	</bibliosource>
</biblioentry>

<biblioentry xml:id="govuk-supercomputers">
	<citetitle>Technology Secretary announces investment boost making British AI supercomputing 30 times more powerful</citetitle>
	<pubdate>1 November 2023</pubdate>
	<publisher>
		<publishername>UK Government</publishername>
	</publisher>
	<bibliosource class="uri">
		<link href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/technology-secretary-announces-investment-boost-making-british-ai-supercomputing-30-times-more-powerful">https://www.gov.uk/government/news/technology-secretary-announces-investment-boost-making-british-ai-supercomputing-30-times-more-powerful</link>
	</bibliosource>
</biblioentry>

<biblioentry xml:id="govuk-invest-ai-taskforce">
	<citetitle>Initial £100 million for expert taskforce to help UK build and adopt next generation of safe AI</citetitle>
	<pubdate>24 April 2023</pubdate>
	<authorgroup>
        <author><orgname>Department for Science, Innovation and Technology</orgname></author>
	<author>
        <personname>
		<firstname>Michelle</firstname>
		<surname>Donelan</surname>
	</personname>
	</author>
	<author>
        <personname>
		<firstname>Rishi</firstname>
		<surname>Sunak</surname>
	</personname>
	</author>

	</authorgroup>
	<bibliosource>
         <link href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/initial-100-million-for-expert-taskforce-to-help-uk-build-and-adopt-next-generation-of-safe-ai">
	https://www.gov.uk/government/news/initial-100-million-for-expert-taskforce-to-help-uk-build-and-adopt-next-generation-of-safe-ai
	 </link>
	</bibliosource>
</biblioentry>

<biblioentry xml:id="ai-history">
	<citetitle>History of artificial intelligence (AI)</citetitle>
	<pubdate>2025</pubdate>
	<publisher>
	<publishername>
		Encyclopædia Britannica Inc
	</publishername>
	</publisher>
	<bibliosource class="uri">
		<link href="https://www.britannica.com/science/history-of-artificial-intelligence">
			https://www.britannica.com/science/history-of-artificial-intelligence
		</link>
	</bibliosource>
</biblioentry>

<biblioentry xml:id="bbc-edinburgh-shelved">
	<citetitle>Government shelves £1.3bn UK tech and AI plans</citetitle>
	<pubdate>2 August 2024</pubdate>
	<author>
		<personname>
			<firstname>Zoe</firstname>
			<surname>Kleinman</surname>
		</personname>
	</author>
	<publisher>
        <publishername>British Broadcasting Corporation</publishername>
	</publisher>
	<bibliosource class="uri">
		<link href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cyx5x44vnyeo">
			https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cyx5x44vnyeo
		</link>
	</bibliosource>
	</biblioentry>

	 <biblioentry id="pm-ai-speech2025">
		 <citebiblioid>grumpy</citebiblioid>
	<title>f1.</title>
    <citetitle>PM speech on AI Opportunities Action Plan</citetitle>
	<author>
        <personname>
	  <honorific>Sir</honorific>
          <firstname>Keir</firstname>
          <surname>Starmer</surname>
        </personname>
        </author>
    <pubdate>13 January 2025</pubdate>
    <publisher>
	<publishername>
	  UK Government
	</publishername>
    </publisher>
    <address>
      <orgname>ULC</orgname>
      <city>London</city>
      <country>United Kingdom</country>
    </address>
    <bibliosource class="uri">
	    <link href="https://www.gov.uk/government/speeches/pm-speech-on-ai-opportunities-action-plan-13-january-2025">
https://www.gov.uk/government/speeches/pm-speech-on-ai-opportunities-action-plan-13-january-2025
    </link></bibliosource>
</biblioentry>

 <biblioentry pubwork="article" id="govuk-press-release-teachers-ai-tools-homework">
	  <title>Teachers to get more trustworthy AI tech, helping them mark homework and save time</title>
	  <pubdate>28 August 2024</pubdate>
	  <author>
					 <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">
			  Department for Science, Innovation and Technology
		  </orgname>
	  </author>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/teachers-to-get-more-trustworthy-ai-tech-as-generative-tools-learn-from-new-bank-of-lesson-plans-and-curriculums-helping-them-mark-homework-and-save">
https://www.gov.uk/government/news/teachers-to-get-more-trustworthy-ai-tech-as-generative-tools-learn-from-new-bank-of-lesson-plans-and-curriculums-helping-them-mark-homework-and-save
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>

 <biblioentry pubwork="webpage" id="stv-teachers-leaving">
	    <author>
	    <orgname class="corporation">
		PA Media
		<uri href="https://pa.media/">https://pa.media</uri>
	    </orgname>
	    </author>
	  <title>Hundreds of new teachers quit profession within five years, figures show</title>
	  <pubdate>5 Janurary 2024</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://news.stv.tv/scotland/hundreds-of-new-teachers-quit-profession-within-five-years-figures-show"></link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
	 <biblioentry id="govuk-one-million-ai-teaching-tools">
			 <pubdate>13 January 2025</pubdate>
			 <authorgroup>
			  <author>
			    <personname>
				<firstname>Bridget</firstname>
				<surname>Phillipson</surname>
			     </personname>
			  </author>
			  <author>
			    <personname>
				<firstname>Peter</firstname>
				<surname>Kyle</surname>
			     </personname>
			  </author>
				 <author>
					 <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">
    Department for Education
					 </orgname>
				 </author>
			 <author>
					 <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">
						 Department for Science, Innovation and Technology
					 </orgname>
				 </author>
			 </authorgroup>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/ai-teacher-tools-set-to-break-down-barriers-to-opportunity">
https://www.gov.uk/government/news/ai-teacher-tools-set-to-break-down-barriers-to-opportunity
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
	</biblioentry>

	<biblioentry id="skynews-civil">
		<citetitle>'Almost certain' civil service staff numbers will be cut in AI efficiency drive, minister says</citetitle>
		<publisher>
			<publishername>Sky News</publishername>
		</publisher>
		<bibliosource>
			<link xlink:href="https://news.sky.com/story/almost-certain-civil-service-staff-numbers-will-be-cut-in-ai-efficiency-drive-minister-says-13327407">https://news.sky.com/story/almost-certain-civil-service-staff-numbers-will-be-cut-in-ai-efficiency-drive-minister-says-13327407</link>
		</bibliosource>
	</biblioentry>

  <biblioentry id="neu-ai-education">
	  <title>Artificial intelligence in education</title>
	  <publisher>
		<publishername>
				National Education Union
		</publishername>
		</publisher>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
	  <link href="https://neu.org.uk/advice/classroom/artificial-intelligence-education">
		  https://neu.org.uk/advice/classroom/artificial-intelligence-education
	  </link>
  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="ai-opportunities-action-plan">
  <title>AI Opportunities Action Plan</title>
  <author>
    <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">
      Secretary of State for Science, Innovation and Technology
    </orgname>
  </author>
  <publisher>
    <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">Crown Copyright</orgname>
  </publisher>
  <pubdate>13 January 2025</pubdate>
  <bibliosource class="isbn">
    <isbn>978-1-5286-5362-6</isbn>
  </bibliosource>
    <revnum>CP1241</revnum>
  <releaseinfo>E03258815 01/25</releaseinfo>
  </biblioentry>
 <biblioentry pubwork="webpage" id="skynews-neu-job-loss-fears">
	    <author>
		<personname>
		<firstname>Alexandra</firstname>
		<surname>Rogers</surname>
		</personname>
	    </author>
	  <title>Teaching unions gear up for fight with Number 10 over AI job-loss fears</title>
	  <pubdate>17 March 2025</pubdate>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://news.sky.com/story/teaching-unions-gear-up-for-fight-with-number-10-over-ai-job-loss-fears-13327798">
https://news.sky.com/story/teaching-unions-gear-up-for-fight-with-number-10-over-ai-job-loss-fears-13327798
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="dofe-technical-report-ai-use">
	  <author>
		  <orgname class="other" otherclass="national-government">Department for Education
	</orgname>
        </author>
	  <title>Use Cases for Generative AI in Education</title>
	  <subtitle>
Building a proof of concept for Generative AI feedback and resource generation in education contexts: Technical report
	  </subtitle>
  <bibliosource class="isbn">
	  <isbn>978-1-83870-564-0</isbn>
  </bibliosource>
  <pubdate>28 August 2024</pubdate>
  <revnum>RR1423</revnum>
  </biblioentry> 
  <biblioentry pubwork="article" id="ldn-gointerest-kids-ai">
	  <citetitle>AI gap: 56% of students want to learn with AI, but UK schools lag behind with just 20% having access to AI in the classroom</citetitle>
	  <corpauthor>
           London Daily News
	  </corpauthor>
	  <pubdate>8 March 2024</pubdate>
	  <biblioentry>
		  <link href="https://www.londondaily.news/ai-gap-56-of-students-want-to-learn-with-ai-but-uk-schools-lag-behind-with-just-20-having-access-to-ai-in-the-classroom/">https://www.londondaily.news/ai-gap-56-of-students-want-to-learn-with-ai-but-uk-schools-lag-behind-with-just-20-having-access-to-ai-in-the-classroom/</link>
	  </biblioentry>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry pubwork="article" id="ofcom-kids-embrace-ai">
	  <citetitle>Gen Z driving early adoption of Gen AI, our latest research shows</citetitle>
	  <pubdate>28 November 2023</pubdate>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>Office of Communications</publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		  <link href="https://www.ofcom.org.uk/internet-based-services/technology/gen-z-driving-early-adoption-of-gen-ai/?utm_source=chatgpt.com"> https://www.ofcom.org.uk/internet-based-services/technology/gen-z-driving-early-adoption-of-gen-ai/?utm_source=chatgpt.com</link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry pubwork="article" id="bbc-scot-cheating-ai">
	  <citetitle>Are Scottish students using AI to cheat their way to a degree?</citetitle>
	  <pubdate>6 March 2025</pubdate>
	  <authorgroup>
		  <author>
		  <personname>
		  <firstname>Kayleigh</firstname><surname>Harvey</surname>
		  </personname>
	  </author>
      <corpauthor>
        <trademark>BBC</trademark>
	British Broadcasting Corporation Scotland News
      </corpauthor>
	  </authorgroup>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>British Broadcasting Corporation</publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <bibliosource class="uri">
		<link href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/ckg88kk1n8jo">https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/ckg88kk1n8jo</link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry pubwork="webpage" id="david-game-college-coursepage">
	   <citetitle>GCSE AI Adaptive</citetitle>
	   <corpauthor>
		<orgname>David Game College</orgname>
	   </corpauthor>
	 <publisher>
	  <publishername>David Game College</publishername>
	  <address>
		  <orgname>David Game College</orgname>
		  <street>31 Jewry Street</street>
		  <city>London</city>
	  </address>
	 </publisher>
 <bibliosource class="uri">
		<link href="https://www.davidgamecollege.com/courses/courses-overview/item/102/gcse-ai-adaptive-learning-programme">https://www.davidgamecollege.com/courses/courses-overview/item/102/gcse-ai-adaptive-learning-programme</link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry pubwork="article" id="skynews-teacherless-class">
	  <citetitle>UK's first 'teacherless' AI classroom set to open in London</citetitle>
	  <pubdate>31 August 2024</pubdate>
	  <author>
		  <personname>
			  <firstname>Mickey</firstname>
			  <surname>Carroll</surname>
		  </personname>
	  </author>
	  <publisher>
		<publishername>Sky News</publishername>
	  </publisher>
 <bibliosource class="uri">
		<link href="https://news.sky.com/story/uks-first-teacherless-ai-classroom-set-to-open-in-london-13200637">https://news.sky.com/story/uks-first-teacherless-ai-classroom-set-to-open-in-london-13200637</link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="nspcc-genai-safeguarding">
  <citetitle>Viewing Generative AI and children’s safety in the round</citetitle>
  <authorgroup>
    <corpauthor>NSPCC</corpauthor>
  </authorgroup>
  <pubdate>January 2025</pubdate>
  <publisher>NSPCC</publisher>
</biblioentry>
<biblioentry>
	<citetitle>Can artificial intelligence replace teachers in schools?</citetitle>
	<pubdate>7 March 2025</pubdate>
	<publisher>
         <publishername>The Institution of Engineering and Technology</publishername>
	</publisher>
	<authorgroup>
		<author class="nonprofit"><orgname>E+T Magazine</orgname></author>
	  <author><personname><firstname>Cris</firstname><surname>Andrews</surname></personname></author>
	</authorgroup>
	<bibliosource>
		<link href="https://eandt.theiet.org/2025/03/07/can-artificial-intelligence-replace-teachers-schools">https://eandt.theiet.org/2025/03/07/can-artificial-intelligence-replace-teachers-schools</link>
	</bibliosource>
</biblioentry>
<biblioentry id="bbc-charai-therapist-bot">
 <citetitle>Character.ai: Young people turning to AI therapist bots</citetitle>
    <author>
	    <personname><firstname>Joe</firstname><surname>Tidy</surname></personname>
    </author>
    <pubdate>5 Janurary 2024</pubdate>
    <publisher><publishername>BBC</publishername></publisher>
    <bibliosource>
	    <link>
https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-67872693
	    </link>
    </bibliosource>
    </biblioentry>
    <biblioentry id="charai-lawsuits">
	    <citetitle>Character.AI Lawsuits</citetitle>
	    <pubdate>March 2025</pubdate>
	    <publisher>
		    <publishername>Social Media Victims Law Center</publishername>
	    </publisher>
	    <bibliosource>
		    <link>https://socialmediavictims.org/character-ai-lawsuits/</link>
	    </bibliosource>
    </biblioentry>
    <biblioentry id="charai-safety-updates">
	    <citetitle>Community Safety Updates</citetitle>
	    <publisher>Character AI</publisher>
	    <link href="https://blog.character.ai/community-safety-    updates/">https://blog.character.ai/community-safety-updates/</link>
    </biblioentry>
    <biblioentry id="nypost-charai-14yo-death">
	    <pubdate>23 October 2024</pubdate>
	    <authorgroup>
		    <author>
			    <orgname>New York Post</orgname>
		</author>
			<author><personname>
					<firstname>Emily</firstname>
					<surname>Crane</surname>
			</personname></author>
	    </authorgroup>
	    <bibliosource>
	    <link href="https://nypost.com/2024/10/23/us-news/florida-boy-14-killed-himself-after-falling-in-love-with-game-of-thrones-a-i-chatbot-lawsuit/">
	    https://nypost.com/2024/10/23/us-news/florida-boy-14-killed-himself-after-falling-in-love-with-game-of-thrones-a-i-chatbot-lawsuit/
	    </link>
    </bibliosource>
    </biblioentry>
    <biblioentry id="independent-lord-holmes">
	    <citetitle>Government urged to bring forward AI regulations which put ‘humans at heart'</citetitle>
	    <pubdate>10 March 2025</pubdate>
	    <authorgroup>
	    <author>
		    <personname>
			    <firstname>Richard</firstname>
			    <surname>Wheeler</surname>
		    </personname>
	    </author>
    </authorgroup>
	    <publisher>
             <publishername>The Independent</publishername>
	     <address><city>London</city><postcode>EC2A 1AH</postcode></address>
	    </publisher>
	    <bibliosource class="uri">
		    <link href="https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/government-house-of-lords-conservative-richmond-lord-b2711891.html">
https://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/government-house-of-lords-conservative-richmond-lord-b2711891.html
		    </link>
	    </bibliosource>
    </biblioentry>
    <biblioentry xreflabel="5" xml:id="deep-thought-wins">
     <title>AI Magazine</title>
     <citetitle>Deep Thought Wins Fredkin Intermediate Prize</citetitle>
     <author>
    <personname>
      <firstname>Hans</firstname>
      <surname>Berliner</surname>
    </personname>
  </author>
  <publisher>
    <publishername>Association for the Advancement of Artificial Intelligence</publishername>
    <address><country>US</country></address>
  </publisher>
  <pubdate>1989</pubdate>
  <volumenum>10</volumenum>
  <issuenum>2</issuenum>
  <bibliosource class="issn">0738-4602</bibliosource>
  <copyright>
	  <holder>AAAI</holder> 
	  <year>1989></year>
  </copyright>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="theverge-google-restaurant">
	  <citetitle>Google’s AI reservation service Duplex is now available in 49 states</citetitle>
	  <pubdate>1 April 2021</pubdate>
     <author>
    <personname>
      <firstname>James</firstname>
      <surname>Vincent</surname>
    </personname>
  </author>
	  <publisher>
           <publishername>The Verge</publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <bibliosource pubwork="article">
		  <link href="https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/1/22361729/google-duplex-ai-reservation-availability-49-us-states">
https://www.theverge.com/2021/4/1/22361729/google-duplex-ai-reservation-availability-49-us-states
		  </link>
	  </bibliosource>
  </biblioentry>
 </bibliography>
</article>
