<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<article>
 <info>
 <title>AI Use for Aided Teaching in Country’s Mainstream Classrooms</title>
 </info>

 <section id="intro">
 <title>Introduction</title>
 <para>
	 Artificial Intelligence is a disruptive technology. The concept has ascended into AI aiding scientific breakthroughs and changing the course of business hiring, among others. Most people today are feeling its force whether they know it or not. We are seeing AI pushed to the top of many agendas,  The UK Government is one of the many organisations worldwide to notice this step change with their reaction being one of strong embrace, by annoucning a self-challenge to lead Britain to becoming one of the great AI superpowers <citation linkend="pm-ai-speech2025"/> and Prime Minister Keir Stramer stating his desire was to “mainline AI into the veins” of the country. 
 </para>
 <para>
	 Education and schooling is a core public service, the Government operates around 50,000 schools
	 give a state to show its size and scale. 

		The plan for the UK Government is to implement the AI oppurtunities Action Plan, set out by Matt Clifford, which contains 50 recommendations 
	 The government has commited to take forward the AI Oppurtunities Action Plan and its 50 recommendations. The action plan details a number of key industries, including healthcare, private 
	 In the government’s proposed initiatives, explicitly mentioned was a direction for teachers to be supported by AI, such as admin tasks. In additional, educators were advised to step-up AI curriculum to students. 
 </para>
 </section>

 <section>
  <para> 
   There were two areas of focus of teaching where the Government are hedging AI, those are: student marking tools; designed to give "tailored feedback" on work, which would handle handwritten and pictorials.  And generative lesson plans. Both share the ilk of scouring public data to produce meaningful outputs, 
  </para>
 </section>

 <sect1 id="content">
 <title>My content</title>
 <para>You can use Docbook to markup your writing.</para>
 <para>Docbook can be transformed into other formats of text.</para>
 </sect1>

 <sect2 id="conclusion">
 <title>Conclusion</title>
 <para>In conclusion, Docbook is simple.</para>
 </sect2>

 <bibliography>
	 <title>Bibliography</title> 
	 <biblioentry id="pm-ai-speech2025">
	<author>
        <personname>
            <firstname>Keir</firstname>
            <surname>Starmer</surname>
        </personname>
        </author>

    <title>PM speech on AI Opportunities Action Plan: 13 January 2025</title>
    <pubdate>13 January 2025</pubdate>
    <publisher>UK Government</publisher>
    <city>London</city>
    <biblioid class="url">https://www.gov.uk/government/speeches/pm-speech-on-ai-opportunities-action-plan-13-january-2025</biblioid>
</biblioentry>
 </bibliography>

</article>
