<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<article>
 <info>
 <title>AI Use for Aided Teaching in Country’s Mainstream Classrooms</title>
 </info>

 <section id="intro">
 <title>Introduction</title>
 <para>
		 Artificial Intelligence (AI) is a disruptive technology, transforming industries such as healthcare, finance, media, and customer service <citation linkend="scotgov-spice-ai-healthcare" />
		 <citation linkend="forbes-how-ai-fraud-detection" />
		 <citation linkend="bbc-ai-production" />
		 <citation linkend="ibm-customer-service-ai" />.
	 Many organisations are integrating AI into their operations to enhance effeciency and productivity. Additionally, new applications and markets have emerged, in part due to AI, such as self-driving cars and virtual assistants. AI has gone mainstream, its effect are being felt by most people, whether they are aware of it or not.
	 </para>
	 <para>
	 to AI is an emerging technogy and produced bundles of new applications and markets, such as self-driving vehicles.  Histronically speaking, AI has spent a large part of its life being unrefined and lacking in pratical use, once commonly existance as a theorised standard.  
		 <para>
		AI has been in development for over 70 years, emerging around the same time as the formal establishment of Computer Science as an academic discipline. While AI has experienced steady growth, today’s emerging trends have accelerated both its development and application, compelling market leaders to embrace AI, the UK Government is one such stakeholder.
		 </para>
		 <para>
			 The Cabinet of the United Kingdom, under both Labour and Conservaative governments, recognised the technological step change and pledged investments in AI development. The Conservative-led government allocated £900 million to various British AI projects, citing economic growth as a key incentive. 
		 </para>
		 In 2025, the government support for AI reached new heights when the Prime Minister announced initiatives to position AI as a central pillar of the UK's economic transformation and the securement of £14 billion worth of investments from the private sector. Keir Starmer, speaking on behalf of his government, declared Britain's ambition to become "one of the great AI superpowers" <citation linkend="pm-ai-speech2025"/>. 
	 </para>
	 <para>
		 Alongside the announced investments, the Prime Minister stated that the government's strategy to embrace AI would "improve public services" and, in turn, transform the lives of working groups, with a specific focus on teachers. Given that teachers make up a large portion of public employees in the UK, this example was an important and relevant point to highlight, especially as public schooling faces increasing challenges. 
	 </para>
		 The National Foundation for Educational Research (NFER) recently found that 90% of teachers in England have considered leaving their jobs due to high workloads. This widespread dissatisfaction further compounds the decline in public schooling, with NFER's forecast indicating severe recruitment shortages.
	 </para>
		  <para>
	 Schools across Britain have experienced a shortfall in filling teacher spots.
	 Education and schooling is one of the UK's core public services, with over 29,000 schools across England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland. The sector employs around 1.23 million people, making up approximately 20% of the UK’s 6.12 million public sector workforce. The education sector and its workforce are approaching a shift in practice driven by AI.
		  </para>
			  <para>
				  The government's AI Opportunities Adviser, Matt Clifford CBE, prepared 50 recommendations emphasising that AI tools should be evaluated from the perspective of their primary users: public services. One recommendation highlighted an AI assistant for lesson planning, expected to save over 15 hours of work, showcasing ongoing AI development for the public sector.
			  </para>

	 The AI Opportunities Action Plan, a comprehensive strategy aimed at maximizing AI adoption, is supported by the Department for Education (DfE). The plan seeks to integrate AI tools into the education system, citing enhanced teacher productivity and job satisfaction.
 </para>
  <para> 
As part of this shift, two AI applications are currently in development: student marking tools, designed to provide "tailored feedback" on student work—including handwritten and pictorial submissions—and a lesson plan generator. From published findings, the teachers expressed the AI's instrumental value and the benefits it could bring, such as time-saving.
  </para>
  <para>
Both applications leverage generative AI—a term consistent with the DfE's classification of such tools—a subclass of artificial intelligence specifically designed to analyse public data and generate meaningful outputs.
  </para>

  <section>
	  <title>What is Generative AI?</title>
	  <para>Generative AI, also referred to as GenAI, creates content, commonly text and audio, based on inputs by the users. To create useful content, the AI relies on deep learning models, 

	  artificial intelligence is trained on vast datasets mostly to favour accuracy of facts, diverse viewpoints and quality of the responses. LLMs can be thought as speaking to someone who has studied to become an expert in a field, more often than not, experts give insightful answers on their specialised subject compared with others. 
	  The consumer market was adorned with AI assistants in recent decades, popular choices being Alexa, Siri, and Google Assistant. Aside from the hands-free utilitarian progress, the evolution in AI was creating computers that qualified for the Turing Test --a thought experiment created by Alan Turing to-- sporting a virtual helper who vocalised their answers, with a natural sounding voice. 
	  However, the conversational open endiness  
  </para>
  </section>

		 <para>
		 One such application 
		 </para>

	 Education and schooling is one of the UK's core public services, with the UK as a whole responsible for over 29,000 schools across England, Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland, filled with a workforce that makes up 25% of the UK's 6.12 million total across all sectors.  

	 give a state to show its size and scale. 

		The plan for the UK Government is to implement the AI oppurtunities Action Plan, set out by Matt Clifford, which contains 50 recommendations 
	 The government has commited to take forward the AI Oppurtunities Action Plan and its 50 recommendations. The action plan details a number of key industries, including healthcare, private 
	 In the government’s proposed initiatives, explicitly mentioned was a direction for teachers to be supported by AI, such as admin tasks. In additional, educators were advised to step-up AI curriculum to students. 
 </para>
 </section>

 <section>
 </section>

 <bibliography>
	 <title>Bibliography</title> 
	 <biblioentry id="pm-ai-speech2025">
	<author>
        <personname>
	  <honorific>Sir</honorific>
          <firstname>Keir</firstname>
          <surname>Starmer</surname>
        </personname>
        </author>
    <title>PM speech on AI Opportunities Action Plan: 13 January 2025</title>
    <pubdate>13 January 2025</pubdate>
    <publisher>UK Government</publisher>
    <city>London</city>
    <biblioid class="url">https://www.gov.uk/government/speeches/pm-speech-on-ai-opportunities-action-plan-13-january-2025</biblioid>
</biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="scotgov-spice-ai-healthcare">
    <abbrev>SPICe 2024</abbrev>
    <authorgroup>
      <author>
        <firstname>Scottish Parliament Information Centre</firstname>
      </author>
    </authorgroup>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence and Healthcare in Scotland</title>
    <publisher>Scottish Parliament Information Centre (SPICe)</publisher>
    <pubdate>25 June 2024</pubdate>
    <url>https://digitalpublications.parliament.scot/ResearchBriefings/Report/2024/6/25/1373556b-9298-42d4-8a24-0e493b84cec9</url>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="forbes-how-ai-fraud-detection">
	  <authorgroup>
		<author>
		<personname>
		  <honorific>Dr</honorific>
		  <firstname>Jeremy</firstname>
		  <surname>Nunn</surname>
		</personname>
		</author>
	  </authorgroup>
	  <title>How AI And Machine Learning Help Detect And Prevent Fraud</title>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>
		   Forbes Media LLC
		  <publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <pubdate>1 November 2023</pubdate>
	  <url>https://www.forbes.com/councils/forbestechcouncil/2023/11/01/how-ai-and-machine-learning-help-detect-and-prevent-fraud/</url>
  </biblioentry>
  <biblioentry id="bbc-ai-production">
    <authorgroup>
      <corpauthor>
        <trademark>BBC</trademark>
	British Broadcasting Corporation
      </corpauthor>
    </authorgroup>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>
                   British Broadcasting Corporation
		  </publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <pubdate>1 Janurary 2017</pubdate>
	  <url>https://www.bbc.co.uk/rd/projects/ai-production</url>
  </biblioentry>
 </bibliography>
 <bibliography id="ibm-customer-service-ai">
    <authorgroup>
      <corpauthor>
        <trademark>IBM</trademark>
	International Business Machines Corporation
      </corpauthor>
    </authorgroup>
	  <publisher>
		  <publishername>
			  International Business Machines Corporation
		  </publishername>
	  </publisher>
	  <pubdate>7 December 2023</pubdate>
	 <url>https://www.ibm.com/think/insights/customer-service-future</url>
 </bibliography>
</article>
